{
    "id": "f7566b270fae47a19d46bda4f18f3f22",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I talked to that shy girl …………………… . she wouldn’t feel left out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is going …………………… .. get a new job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped at the pub …………………. a drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Is that cake …………………… eating?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Should I get anything ………………… . dinner?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The shirt was too big for me, so I took it back to the shop ……………………… get a replacement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We started early …………………… . we wouldn’t be late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Take some water ……………………… drink on the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You need a licence ……………………… drive a four wheeler.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am leaving a bit early today ………………….. I won’t get stuck in the rush hour traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}